trackingkit.com 2016-01-17

# Privacy Policy

Last Modified: 09 March 2015

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.TrackingGo.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving our website. By using this website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

###### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

You can generally visit the website without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. TrackingGo.com automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. We may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see to fulfill your request for certain services. We never leak this non-personal data collected from you to others or for other use without your permission.

###### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

###### Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website.

###### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

###### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

###### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [trackinggo(DOT)outlook.com.](mailto:trackinggo@outlook.com)
